# Tomasz Żuber

#### **Informations**

in tomaszz95



in/tomasz-zuber95



tomaszzportfolio.vercel.app



tzuber95@gmail.com



remote / willing to relocate

#### **Education**

2014 - 2019

**Mining Surveying** Silesian University of Technology Master's Degree

## **Work Experience**

2021 - Currently **Land Surveyor Specialist** Asgeodezja Sp. z o. o. Mikołów

2019 - 2021 **Land Surveyor** Land surveying services, Mikołów

#### **Soft Skills**

- Teamwork
- Problem solving
- Effective communication
- Good time management
- Attention to details
- Learning from mistakes
- Responsibility

## Languages

- Polish native
- English B2

### Interests

- Modern technologies
- Hiking
- Bushcraft
- Piano playing

#### About me

I am an aspiring frontend junior developer who is disciplined, ambitious, hard-working, and ready to continuously expand my programming knowledge and further develop my skills. I have been learning programming for more than two years and have reached the point where my current goal is to get my first position as a frontend developer. My technological stack and skills enable me to apply for most positions at the 'junior' or 'intern' level - unfortunately I only lack commercial experience. My goal for the future is to evolve into a full-stack developer by enhancing my skills in database maintenance and backend development.

### **Projects**

#### Portfolio – a simple portfolio page with more information about me

*Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/mainsite* 

Live: https://tomaszzportfolio.vercel.app

This is a fully functional and responsive portfolio website, with more information about me, the projects I have created, the technologies I use and ways to contact me. Additionally, the website features a form that allows you to send me a message directly.

Stack: NextJS, React, Typescript, Tailwind, Git/Github, RWD, SEO, Accessibility.

#### Netflix clone – fully responsive website, which is an advanced clone of the popular streaming service Netflix, with many of its features

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/Netflixclone

Live: https://nerflixcloneen.vercel.app

A website that is a 'clone of Netflix' – it is fully responsive, with best SEO and accessibility practices and with many features from the original streaming site. The application includes numerous sub-pages, ranging from the main view to the registration and login processes, profile selection and editing, as well as the main pages for series, movies, individual sub-pages, and search pages. This is my most significant and advanced project to date - the app is built with approximately 250 components and encompasses around 30 different subpages, including the dynamic ones.

Stack: NextJS, React, Typescript, Firebase, CSS, Git/Github, RWD, SEO, Accessibility.

#### **Gradebook** – an online app for students and teachers

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/gradebook

Live: https://gradebookk.vercel.app

An application that partially mimics the operation of an electronic gradebook. The app enables you to check your timetable, grades, statistics related to the grades, and comparisons with other students/classes. As a teacher, you can add news and assign grades to individual students. It combines frontend with backend and retrieving data from databases.

Stack: NextJS, React, Typescript, Firebase, MongoDB, CSS, Git/Github, SEO, Accessibility.

#### Toolkit – a website with several apps: Todo List, Notes, Calculator, Financial management, Weather App

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/toolkit

*Live: https://toolkiit.netlify.app* 

A website with the most popular frontend projects written in React, using React Redux and React Router, as well as Local Storage. The page is fully responsive.

Stack: React, React Redux, CSS, Git/Github, RWD, SEO, Accessibility.

#### Tech Skills / Stack

- NextJS
- React Redux
- Tailwind
- CSS/SCSS
- Git/Github
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB

- React
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- HTML
- RWD, SEO
- Tailwind
- Firebase

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).